and psychic forces.
L.H. Anderson, I've been thumbing
through this one a lot here lately.
I've actually been putting my own little
notes in it. Maybe someday somebody will
read them.
Okay.
All right.
Hold it down like this.
Hold down like this.
All right.
And then you hold it like this.
You have to update the app probably.
Why don't you just use this hand?
Oh boy.
Does this look like it's coming in right
or crooked?
I think you can just take this and
double click on it, but those are
crooked. So
And that's going to be your hands when
you grab this. Hold this like this, and
then I kind of want that black out of
there.
So I need to start over? No, you can
just delete those, but go back a couple
of pages. Okay.
And then um I just started.
We got the first one, right? Mhm.
So, that's really really hard. Mhm.
That's a very uh
a nice and easy
process.
Okay, that's good.
That one is good. All right.
Here's to
Oh, hello YouTube.
Uh there's no message function on
YouTube, so I don't get to talk to you
much. And if you want to holler at me,
now's your chance.
All right, and say hello to Facebook.
Hello Facebook, too.
We have everybody in here. Yay.
Everybody's here. So, let's see
if that's good.
Looks better.
Let's see this one.
And there we go.
You should do
I'm going to put this
All right.
You can just set it up probably up on
this thing somewhere you can see. Okay.
Uh
well, that doesn't fall down. It's okay.
There you go.
I think
Uh
>> [sighs]
>> hello, hello.
And then there's YouTube as well.
It's kind of strange.
Sitting here scanning a book with uh
lots of people watching me.
So, that needs to be on there.
Let's see.
>> [sighs]
>> See, look at those. They keep coming in
there skewed.
This is not as easy it would look. Uh
I'm honest.
Hey New York, what's up? And then I can
start here. I'm going to start over
again.
And then
I don't need this.
Okay. Click.
And then when you go down to flip the
page, you can kind of
And then straighten up, let it quit
moving, and then click again.
All right.
Mhm.
You don't have to think
>> Yeah, y'all think this is easy. It's not
as easy as it would look.
Um everybody's like, "Hey, you scan the
Bible a little bit." Watch those red
lines. Mhm. Okay.
And then the other side even while it's
loading, it doesn't count anything. It
just There you go. as they're going
through.
Hello Las Vegas.
Um
All right. [clears throat]
Australia, hey baby.
And uh the lovely Alex is here, too.
Alex, if there's any people on YouTube
who would like to ask me a question. No,
blinded by the light.
Puerto Rico.
And then boom.
No, not easy. How many books are we in
now?
Three? I [snorts] don't know.
>> Four? There's an endless amount of
books. But it's like the first three
books that we did were those massive
Bibles, so that took a hot minute.
Wishing you every success imaginable in
your studies and experiences, hoping
that you will use the benefits that you
receive to the honor of our creator and
to the profit of your neighbor. Remember
our instructions to be silent, talk only
with those who
talk only with those worthy of
communication, do not give pearls to
swine, be friendly with all but not
familiar with all for many are as the
scriptures mentioned wolves in sheep's
clothing. Sincerely yours, L.A. J.
Anderson. Which book is this?
This is Ancient Magic, Magnetism and
Psychic Forces by L.A. J. Anderson,
Masonic Temple 1895.
Right here it says
kept under the cloak of religion.
And you can see I've gone through this
one a whole lot this far.
Ohio, Nashville, all kinds of people in
here today.
I said you knew exactly what book it was
just from the the short videos and the
tabs.
I don't know what I do here.
How are you doing?
Uh-huh.
Say yes.
Mhm.
Do you all think we should just have
these here for people who come to
reality to view? Um I mean I have the
books. I read them. I know y'all see
them online Let's watch that middle
line.
I want this one center.
Okay.
So it's kind of like a little dance with
these papers every time.
Yeah, I don't want to hurry it though.
See how it's crazy?
>> Uh lots of questions on where they can
find these books.
Right now at my house in Costa Rica.
>> [laughter]
>> Um
I realized that I have a whole lot of
stuff here that not many people have
access to and I'm doing the best I can
to get it out there.
This is a a
road to walk, guys. Um
I will tell you, the more you go about
spreading truth, the harder things will
attack you. I've left field.
My life is proof of that.
And you know,
Go for the middle. Okay.
And uh
And then let's see where that black one
is right on the page line, kind of. Mhm.
Maybe here.
>> Somewhere here. Mhm.
Pink. Maybe. We'll see.
There you go.
So So that right there needs to be lined
up with the page. And then try and get
your arm and hand up. Do y'all want to
hear a part of this one? They do want
you to read it out loud at least. Okay.
I'll read You got to understand in these
old books, it's really like one sentence
with 14 commas
is an entire paragraph.
So I'll I'll read some of the stuff I've
actually uh underlined in here.
This is talking about the simulation.
By far the greater part of mankind lives
on imagination. Not only the less
instructed natural men of feeling, but
even those who boast of knowledge and a
higher mental cultivation. How few in
their feelings and sufferings and their
doings and
and aspirings raise themselves in the
sea of life above the world of
imagination.
In the literary hero romance among the
scenes of the stage, there is no more
original thought than in the persevering
church goer.
The great mass wishes to be devout and
thinks that the glorification of God's
name lies in miracles rather than
natural action. Dignity, riches, and
power are only too much the springs of
even great and eminent minds.
>> [clears throat]
>> There's a whole lot of stuff in here.
I'm interested in some
What's the purpose of this project?
Well,
when I started reading these books, I
was just blown away. I mean,
I've been reading books my whole life,
you know, I grew up without a TV.
Should I pull my boots off? Uh
let's see how hot it's getting on it.
Well,
no.
I'd leave them on there. They're part of
history, aren't they? Wait, wait, grab
this one with you. Do we take the boots
off or do we leave them on?
I think leave them
All right.
We can leave them on.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. It's good. It's good.
I can feel it from on there. You see, in
here he's he's talking about
the best thing that can be said of
miracles is the answer given by Christ
to Nicodemus. That which is born of
flesh is flesh, and that which is born
of spirit is spirit.
So, I mean, he quotes the Bible a lot in
here.
Did we already get that one? Yes.
Okay. See, I I'm losing my place. Yes,
that's what happens.
Focus.
All right.
Pink.
Okay.
I'm going Hey, sorry about the Wi-Fi is
cutting out. We're in this enclosed AC
block room just to keep all the Bibles
safe, but the the Wi-Fi kind of cuts out
in here a bit.
Mhm.
Let's scan that one.
Yep.
Wendy said she's never been more excited
in her life to read something.
Who? Wendy. Oh.
Here it goes.
Mhm.
I'm going to scan this whole book in
here.
I mean, the pictures are pretty cool,
too. I think you should go over some of
the tabs like have them what it says.
Oh.
I mean,
in
But, you know, you [clears throat] can
read anything and if you believe it,
it's real. And if you don't believe it,
it's not real.
Um
this chapter is entitled magic, black
and white. And he quotes Pythagoras at
the beginning.
Man may become by the assistance and
cooperation of spiritual powers and
capacities of his higher divine origin
capable of a higher sphere of activity
within as well as without himself, which
gives him
over his own and over surrounding
nature.
You know,
you kind of got to chew this
information, which is why I want to put
it online. Um
there's a whole lot
of info in here that
you read it, you have to think about it.
It doesn't just make sense
automatically. And I put little notes
and everything all in here trying to
make sense of uh
of these books.
Should I move this?
>> want to know, do you think traveling to
Jerusalem Jerusalemism
Jerusalem
I'll be with your investigation of the
Bible so you are getting I am not going
anywhere near the Middle East right now.
Are you kidding me?
No me voy. No me voy. Yo hablo español.
Uno razon.
No, no, no. I'm not going to the Middle
East anytime soon.
Um
I'll say hi to Jab.
Julian.
Hey, Julian Brown.
Coming out of my cave, homie. Trying to.
I miss you, dog. I could use your help.
When I say help, I mean, I don't know,
some fun time.
I took you to the river.
Yeah, you did. Alex has been trying to
fix on me for days now, haven't you?
Years.
Is it working? Yeah.
>> [snorts]
>> Okay.
So,
>> [clears throat]
>> right here.
We find many
All right, let me just start here. Let
us turn again to the history of the
people of Israel into the early oriental
nations and compare the magic among them
that of later ages.
Wait a minute.
It says, "The people of Israel and the
early oriental nations and compare their
magic to the magic of the later ages." I
mean, they're You're sitting sitting
here saying there's a whole lot of magic
going on for a long time.
In the first place, as I've already
remarked, the Israelites stood alone
among all the surrounding pagan nations
and magic among them had [clears throat]
a peculiar form. For although the Jews
had spent so long a time in Egypt, they
carried with them but little of its
magic, that is, of the real theurgic
magical arts which are perfected by
natural powers and human inventions. The
magical ecstasies and miracles were
rather inspirations of divine power and
the influence of the black art producing
supernatural effects by natural means
was forbidden under the severest
penalties.